http://www.lfcu.org/about/privacy.aspx

Skip to main content
Please be advised that our Cabin John branch is currently experiencing connectivity issues, impacting ATM, internet and phone services. We are working diligently to bring these services back online. Thank you for your patience during this time.
Download App
AbouteServicesRatesFormsLocationsATMsOpen AccountApply for a LoanMake a PaymentContact(301) 929-7990+1 (800) 888-6560 (toll-free)M - F, 8:30 a.m. - 4:00 p.m. Audio Response 24/7Email UsLogin into Online BankingOpens in New Windowfor account-specific questionsMore Contact OptionsSite Search
Serving members worldwide since 1935.
PersonalBusinessLoginOpens in New Window
PersonalBankBankCheckingSavingsMoney MarketDirect DepositATM & Debit CardAccount AccessOther Banking ServicesWe're ready when you are. Join the credit union or open a secondary account securely online 24/7.Open an AccountBorrowBorrowAuto & Motorcycle LoansBoat & RV LoansCredit Card Mortgage LoansHome EquityPersonal LoansApply for your loan securely 24/7 in just 5-10 minutes. You can even save your application to finish later.Apply for a LoanMake a PaymentInvestInvestIRAsCoverdell Education SavingsShare CertificatesInvestment ServicesTrusts & Custodial AccountsConvenience Person (POA)Now is the time to be preparing for the future. We can help you prioritize your goals and set your savings on autopilot. Get StartedProtectProtectOverdraft Protection Auto InsuranceIdentity Theft ProtectionHomeowner's InsuranceLife and AD&D InsuranceLoan ProtectionSome risks aren't worth taking. Protect yourself and your family. Offset high risk with affordable insurance policies so you can rest easy. Find Your PolicyLearnLearnBuying a CarBuying a HouseProtecting Your IdentityManaging Money & CreditPlanning for RetirementYouth & Student Finances
BusinessBusiness BankingBusiness LendingManagement ServicesEmployee BankingResources
AbouteServicesRatesFormsLocationsATMsOpen AccountApply for a LoanMake a PaymentContact
Return to Content
We Value Your Privacy
Review our policies to understand how we use the information you provide to us.
Privacy PolicyNot a Member?Enjoy the benefits of credit union membership, including:Lower lending ratesHigher dividend ratesFewer or lower feesWe offer free access to thousands of ATMs nationwide. Visit any of our eight convenient branches in Maryland, Virginia and Washington, D.C.Or visit a shared branch — there's at least one in every state!Join Today!Opens in New WindowWhat do we do with your information?Privacy PolicyFinancial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. What Does Lafayette Federal Credit Union Do With Your Information?Why? Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.What?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and payment historyCreditworthiness and credit historyHow?All financial companies need to share members’ personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their members’ personal information; the reasons Lafayette Federal chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.Reasons we can share your personal informationDoes Lafayette Federal share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes —such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes —to offer our products and services to youYesYesFor joint marketing with other financial companiesYesNoFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —information about your transactions and experiencesYesNoFor our affiliates’ everyday business purposes —information about your creditworthinessNoWe do not shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNoWe do not shareWho we areWho is providing this notice?Lafayette Federal Credit Union and Home Ownership Financial Literacy Council (HOFLC)What we doHow does Lafayette Federal protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to guard your non-public personal information.How does Lafayette Federal collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youopen an account or deposit moneypay your bills or apply for a loanuse your credit or debit cardbrowse our websiteWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus, affiliates, or other companies. We use cookies to collect data from our website.Why can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit only:sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes — information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.What happens when I limit sharing for an account I hold jointly with someone else?Your choices will apply to everyone on your account.DefinitionsAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.We will partner only with businesses that follow strict confidentiality requirements.NonaffiliatesNon-affiliates may include: insurance companies, direct marketing companies, credit card networks.Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.We may disclose non-public personal information about our members and former members to non-affiliated third parties as permitted by law.Joint Marketing Joint marketing partners may include investment services, insurance, or credit card networks.A formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.We have a contractual relationship that prohibit the third party from disclosing or using the information of our agreement.Other important informationWe restrict access to non-public personal information about you to: employees and volunteers who need to know that information to provide products or services to you; our attorneys, accountants, and auditors on a need-to-know basis; government authorities to comply with federal, state, or local laws, rules and other applicable legal requirements; consumer reporting agencies in accordance with the Fair Credit Reporting Act. Our credit union is committed to making financial products and services available that will enable you to meet your financial needs and reach your financial goals while at the same time protecting your personal information and using it in a manner consistent with your expectations.Protecting your personal information is a high priority for everyone associated with our credit union! This notice is available upon request.Questions?Call 301-929-7990 or visit WWW.LFCU.ORGTo opt out:Call 301-929-7990 or email memberservice@lfcu.orgEffective June 2020Internet Privacy Policy Information Collected and Stored AutomaticallyFor site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, we employ software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.For site management, information may be collected for statistical purposes. Computer software programs may be used to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas. No personal information, such as your name or address, is collected or used for this analysis. We collect no information which would identify you personally.Information Collected from Emails and Web FormsWhen you send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment or by filling out a form or application that emails us this information, we use this information to fulfill or respond to your requests. We may store these requests to support the application process. We may forward your email to staff who are better able to respond to your request. We do not create individual profiles with the information you provide.Have questions?Contact Us
Knowledge is power. Be in the know for financial betterment.
Buying a CarBuying a HouseProtecting Your IdentityManaging Money & CreditPlanning for RetirementYouth & Student Finances
Holiday LoanCheers to extra GREEN for you this holiday season with a Lafayette Federal Holiday Loan!
Rates as low as 4.74% APR*
Shared Branches & ATMsOur members have access to Co-Op Network Shared Branches & ATMs for all basic transaction needs.
Access branches and ATMs nationwide
Schedule a Branch VisitVisit one of our eight branch locations, conveniently located in DC, Maryland and Virginia.Schedule a branch visit today
(301) 929-7990
Lafayette Federal Credit Union is one of the premiere financial institutions in the Washington, D.C. area, now serving DXC and CSRA employees. Since our founding in 1935, we have sought to provide our members with a safe and convenient place to save, and to offer loans at rates and terms more favorable than those of other financial institutions. We also work hard to provide top-notch customer service. Contact us to obtain a copy of our Annual Report.
Become a SEGCalculatorsCareersDisclosuresFeesPrivacyWeb AccessibilitySecuritySitemap
Toll-Free+1 (800) 888-6560Lost Card?Debit: +1 (888) 918-7802Credit: +1 (800) 449-7728Routing #: 254074811
Branch LocationsMarylandKensington, MD 20895Potomac, MD 20854Rockville, MD 20852VirginiaCrystal City, VA 22202McLean, VA 22101
Washington, DCPennsylvania Avenue, NW 3rd Street, SW Kenyon Street, NWFind a Branch or ATMHoliday Closings
Opens in New WindowProud Member 2020Opens in New Window
© 2020 Lafayette Federal Credit Union | Federally Insured by NCUAOpens in New WindowEqual Opportunity Employer | E-Verify EmployerOpens in New WindowSite by VisionsOpens in New Window
